<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technician. Musician. Writer. on Chris Walker</title>
    <link>https://christianwalker.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technician. Musician. Writer. on Chris Walker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2020 Chris Walker</copyright><atom:link href="https://christianwalker.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://christianwalker.me/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christianwalker.me/music/</guid>
      <description>Since the age of 13, Chris has been playing the guitar. He later picked up drums and has always sang; and this lead to a hobbyist career in music.
Chris has played in numerous bands throughout the years; most recently as a session guitarist and collaborator for Martyn Peters. He has also played in a 22 piece Rhythm and Blues Orchestra; in the pit for a production of Jason Robert Brown&amp;rsquo;s The Last Five Years as well as recording, mixing and mastering his own music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology</title>
      <link>https://christianwalker.me/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christianwalker.me/tech/</guid>
      <description>Through a serendipitous job offer from a friend at University, Chris began a career in Technology installing bespoke, outdoor-ready wireless and internet solutions into music festivals. After two years working at the likes of Glastonbury, Leeds and T in the Park, he moved into IT Support, specialising in Apple machines. After a 7 year term at the University of Chester, working in imaging and deployment, Chris is now a Team Leader at razorblue, a national Managed Service Provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://christianwalker.me/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christianwalker.me/writing/</guid>
      <description>It was only a matter of time for Chris began writing, given that his Mum is a published author of both fiction and reference books. At his role at razorblue, Chris has authored a number of technical documents relating to IT processes, the clarity of which is essential for their engineers.
In a more journalistic capacity, Chris has written for Thryve.world as a travel and adventure writer; describing adventures in the Lake District on two wheels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
